## LEA HAZEL

San Diego, CA • linkedin.com/in/leamhazel • GitHub: lmhazel

Detail-oriented, driven, and enthusiastic full-stack web developer with a background in social sciences and law, transitioning into the world of tech. Experienced in numerous people-oriented positions that would be perfectly applicable for working successfully in development teams.

### **SKILLS**

**Languages/Libraries/Frameworks:** React, JavaScript, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, SQL, HTML/CSS, Python, R, Slim, ES6, jQuery

Testing: JEST, RSPEC

Technologies: Postman, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Version Control/Git, GitHub,

General: Microsoft Excel and Word, qualitative data collection, academic research, data analytics, social sciences

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Full Stack Web Developer (Intern)

Mar 2023-Present

Ceatus Media Group, Remote

- Added UI features to internal tools, for example sorting indicators on table headers, hover tooltips for project descriptions, clickable routing to project pages, etc.
- Updated styles to maintain consistency across the internal applications, following design directives

#### Full Stack Web Development Student

Nov 2022-Mar 2023

LEARN Academy, Remote

- Gained experience in working with multiple front and back-end languages and created full-stack applications through the implementation of Test Driven Development
- Completed over 480 hours of coding experience using individual and pair-programming

#### **Assistant Instructor**

Jan 2023-Mar 2023

LEARN Academy, Remote

- Assisted in teaching Jumpstart, a 3-day bootcamp for prospective LEARN students focused around HTML, CSS, and fundamental JavaScript
- Successfully and effectively instructed students on creating a fully coded website

#### **Contract Specialist**

Sept 2022-Nov 2022

MD7, San Diego, CA

- Interpreted and handled highly sensitive financial and legal documents
- Discussed with 8-12 landlords and property management companies a day in order to resolve rent related issues

#### Campaign Organizer

Mar 2022-Oct 2022

Berkeley Unified School District Board of Education Campaign, Berkeley, CA

- · Managed social media (Twitter, Instagram, FaceBook) to promote campaign resulting in many daily engagers and supporters
- Engaged with stakeholders/community members at public events
- · Learned structures and strategies of a campaign and applying material through organizing events and canvassing

# **Legal Assistant (Intern)**

Nov 2021-Apr 2022

Argumedo Garzon Law Group, San Francisco, CA

- Analyzed court motions in law office and at San Francisco Immigration Court
- · Assisted head attorneys in preparation for court hearings and client meetings through research and paperwork
- · Familiarized myself with the complexities of relationships among immigration attorneys, clients, and court

#### **EDUCATION**

### University of California, Berkeley

Bachelor of Arts, Sociology May 2022

Relevant Coursework: Critical Reasoning and Writing | Research Method for Psychology | Seminar and Research in Sociology

## Coursera, Remote

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate July 2022

Skills Acquired: data cleaning, analysis, & visualization, Rstudio, R Markdown, Tableau Software, Metadata, and spreadsheets